HOANG THAI DUONG

Frontend Developer

+84918475646

duongtantien1@gmail.com

38/7 Street No.5, Linh Trung Ward, Thu Duc City

SUMMARY

I am a dedicated Developer specializing in ReactJS and NextJS. Passionate about web development, I constantly seek opportunities to learn and grow in this field. I strive to stay updated with the latest technologies to create modern and efficient web applications.

EXPERIENCE

04/2023 - Now

Frontend developer at Shinhan DS Viet Nam

Main Responsibilities:

- Integrated React into the project to enhance frontend capabilities.
- Developed a human resources management system. Expand responsibilities to develop a system for constructing an environment to initiate messages and databases for Korean partners.
- Collaborate with Korean development team to create CRUD, management admin pages.

Main Achievements:

- Successfully implemented and applied React to the company's existing applications.
- Developed a successful website for constructing databases and messaging systems for partners.
- Built a website for initiating orders and showcasing products/service for partners.

Technologies:

- Typescript, JavaScript, ReactJs, MUI, Vite, TailwindCss, Antd, Storybook **Project:**
- ProjectTM (4 phases), Madiv-One, HRMs.

11/2022 - 03/2023

Intern Frontend developer at FPT Software

Main Responsibilities:

• Participate in developing and building advertising and tourist room rental websites. Deployed services for websites, ensuring seamless implementation and optimal functionality.

Main Achievements:

• Deploy and complete projects and hand over to customers.

Technologies:

• Reactjs, MUI, Typescript, MongoDB.

SKILLS

Typescript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS.

ReactJS, NextJS, NodeJS(Expressjs).

React hooks, React query, Redux toolkit,

React hook form, Class validator.

Tailwind, MUI, Antd, Radix, Bootstrap.

MongoDB.

Github, Gitlab.

Redmine, Jira.

Agile.

PROJECTS

OwwiMoney(Reactjs, Nextjs)

Github: https://github.com/thoaiIT/OwwiMoney

Demo: https://owwimoney.vercel.app

Twitter(Nodeis)

Github: https://github.com/hoangthaiduong2001/node_twitter

COMMUNICATION

Collaborate effectively with engineers, designers, and product managers to ensure alignment and successful project delivery. Provide constructive feedback and suggestions to improve code quality and team collaboration.

EDUCATION

07/2019 - 07/2024

UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Degree in Information Systems Engineer